# CHAD LISCINSKY

1850 NW Front Ave. Portland, Oregon | 415 505 5859 | chadliscinsky@gmail.com | LinkedIn | chadliscinsky.com

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Customer Success, Sales and Account Management Professional with a proven record of positive results executing strategic plans to meet company objectives. Highly experienced creating essential partnerships and lasting relationships with current and prospective clients. Technology focused, problem solver and here to make the workplace an exciting and inspiring environment to thrive in. My passion for growth, success and new technology combined with my creative drive keeps customers engaged while bringing their visions to life.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## VIP CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER | ZOOMINFO, VANCOUVER, WA

November 2020 – Present

- Manage 132+ accounts | VIP Mid-Market book of business with total account ACV exceeding \$15 million
- Work directly with Onboarding and Integration managers ensuring proper adoption and ongoing engagement throughout the customers lifecycle
- Drive adoption across multiple departments, stakeholders and business users
- Perform multiple touchpoints throughout the contract cycle including strategic quarterly business reviews with focus on overall growth, ROI and mitigating risk/churn
- Develop success plans for customers that outline their critical success factors, metrics for success, potential issues, and provide recommendations
- Present product utilization data to clients to ensure they are full value from products and services with focus on providing consistent exceptional support
- Work directly with CX team leads identifying possible risk to proactively mitigate logo churn
- Manage complete Customer lifecycle/Health within Gainsight and Salesforce CRM

## DIRECTOR OF SALES | ENCORE EVENT TECHNOLOGIES, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

June 2017 - August 2020

- Developed and executed a highly successful engagement strategy that proactively maintains customer satisfaction leading to a consistent customer capture and retention rate of 94%+
- Led and mentored a skilled team of Account Executives generating a 17%+ Increase in overall revenues while surpassing all personal quotas
- Successfully maintained business for over 30 Enterprise level accounts with individual overall revenues ranging from \$100k 400k annually.
- Engaged and managed full sales cycles ranging from 6 months to two years

• Integrated technical expertise and demonstrations of product with industry best practices for all customers leading to the positive execution of large complex events for top Enterprise clientele

#### SENIOR ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE | PSAV, SAN FRANCISCO, CA

June 2014 - May 2017

- Managed the Enterprise tech, corporate and association business utilizing a 360 degree sales approach ensuring capture and retention rates of 90%+
- Consistently top 3<sup>rd</sup> or above revenue generating Account Executive in the west super region with average yearly revenue totals of \$3.5 million+
- Develop new business from lead stage while engaging sales cycles from 1 month to a year
- Worked directly with clients and producers to develop and provide them with new concepts for their events including CAD development and production schedule securing flawless events

## INSIDE SALES ASSOCIATE | TICKETFLY SAN FRANCISCO, CA

March 2012 - June 2014

- Prospected leads within specific verticals to provide the senior sales team with qualified appointments averaging 20 solid appointments per week
- Responsible for all sales activities, from lead generation to signed agreements with a consistent sales cycle of 1 6 months
- Developed and maintained a complete database of leads and clients within Salesforce CRM
- Demonstrated product knowledge to allow for effective presentation of Ticketfly's software and services leading to an overall increase in demand for the platform.

#### **SKILL HIGHLIGHTS**

Customer Success HTML5 Account Management
Relationship Building CSS3 Business Development
Leadership Gainsight Customer Experience
Problem solving Salesforce CRM Results

#### **EDUCATION**

New England Institute of Art Bachelor of Arts, Audio Production

### **ACTIVITIES**

Music, Film, Travel, Production, Audio, Computer Technology, Outdoors and Food